Finding Aid for Ivory Photo, Ann Arbor, Michigan ca. 1927-1971
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Negatives-- 4"x5"
  - Ann Arbor
    - Buildings and Views
      - Houses and Businesses
        - Packard
          - near State -- apartment building under construction 1963 (Box 4)
          - 709
            - Freeman and Clague Grocery circa 1940, 2 negatives (Box 4)
            - Freeman Grocery -- interior 1952 (Box 4)
          - 713 -- Packard Self-Service Laundry
            - Interior with customers 1950, 5 negatives (Box 4)
            - Interior January 24, 1955, 2 negatives (Box 4)
          - 716 (Box 4)
            (See: Ann Arbor -- Buildings and Views -- Gas Stations -- Sinclair)
          - 727 -- apartment building under construction circa 1967 (Box 4)
          - 909 -- house and garage January 10, 1939, 3 negatives (Box 4)
          - 915 -- El Prado apartments -- front and rear May 4, 1965, 3 negatives (Box 4)
          - 1200 -- Clague's Grocery
            - Interior -- food display 1951 (Box 4)
            - Exterior and interior with shoppers 1952, 3 negatives (Box 4)
              (See also: Ann Arbor -- Buildings and Views -- Gas Stations -- Shell)
          - 1924 -- stores circa 1966 (Box 4)
          - 1928 -- Big Ten Market -- exterior and interior 1953, 3 negatives (Box 4)
          - 2111 -- Kroger Store under construction March 13, 1951, 2 negatives (Box 4)
          - 2326 -- house circa 1953 (Box 4)
          - 3152 -- Styleway Beauty Shop -- interior September 13, 1960 (Box 4)
          - 3309 -- house circa 1957, 2 negatives (Box 4)
          - 4230 -- WHRV radio station 1953 (Box 4)
        - Pauline
          - 506 -- Herbert Busch house January 1954, 2 negatives (Box 4)
        - Pontiac
          - 1010 -- Hilbert's Garage
            - August 1953 (Box 4)
            - Exterior with trucks 1950s (Box 4)
        - Sanford Place?
          - 1725 -- house and yard 1957 (Box 4)
        - Saunders Crescent
          - 1531 -- Dr. Kahn's house -- interior circa 1960, 7 negatives (Box 4)
        - Spring Street
          - 1109 -- Leonard Boddy house circa 1935 (Box 4)
        - Stadium Boulevard, East
          - 1423 -- Ann Arbor Food and Drug Mart -- interior with customers 1951, 3 negatives (Box 4)
          - 1500 (Box 4)
            (See: Ann Arbor -- Buildings and Views -- Gas Stations -- Gulf)
          - 1700 -- house circa 1953 (Box 4)
        - Stadium Boulevard, West
          - 2075 -- United States Post Office under construction June 25, 1959, 2 negatives (Box 4)
          - 2245 -- Henderson Ford circa 1970 (Box 4)
          - 2310 -- Hannah Construction Company and Studio of Interiors -- exterior and interior displays 1948, 5 negatives (Box 4)
          - 2350 -- Wrigley's Grocery Store -- exterior and interiors 1952, 3 negatives (Box 4)
          - 2355-2357 -- Federal Mogul Research and Benz Motors, Inc. circa 1951 (Box 4)
          - 2357 -- Benz Motors, Inc. circa 1951 (Box 4)
          - 2355 -- National Sanitation Foundation
            - Exterior and interior with men, early 1960s, 3 negatives (Box 4)
            - Exterior and interior with people October 5, 1967, 5 negatives (in 3 envelope) (Box 4)
            - Exterior circa 1967, 2 negatives (Box 4)
              (See also: Ann Arbor -- Businesses)
          - 2370 -- Stadium Laundry -- interior circa 1956 (Box 4)
          - 2465 -- Arlan's Department Store -- interior September 2, 1966, 2 negatives (Box 4)
          - 2545 -- Kroger -- exterior and interior display August 31, 1953, 2 negatives (Box 4)
        - State Street, South
          - 214 -- Goldman Cleaners -- exterior and interior July 26, 1954, 5 negatives (Box 4)
          - 215-231 -- State Theater circa 1950 (Box 4)
          - 24-226 -- Kroger Grocery circa 1928-1930 (Box 4)
          - 224 -- Campus Drug
            See: Ann Arbor -- Businesses -- Varsity Laundry, June 1948
            - Interior 1953 (Box 4)
          - 235 -- Marshall's Drug -- exterior and interior May 1952, 2 negatives (Box 4)
          - 302 -- Campus Indoor Archery, early 1930s (Box 4)
          - 303 -- Wagner and Company men's clothing -- display windows, late 1940s-early 1960s, 32 negatives (Box 4)
          - 306 -- Randall's -- women's apparel -- interior with clerk 1952, 6 negatives (Box 4)
          - 307-309 -- Cousins Shop -- women's wear -- interior with clerk circa 1956, 5 negatives (Box 4)
          - 311 -- Wild and Company -- clothing
            - Fall 1950 (Box 4)
            - July 3, 1954 (Box 4)
          - 312 -- Chester Roberts Gifts -- window displays
            - November 15, 1950 (Box 4)
            - December 1950 (Box 4)
            - January 1951 (Box 4)
            - March 9, 1951 (Box 4)
            - April 7, 1951 (Box 4)
            - May 23, 1951 (Box 4)
          - 313 -- Granada Caf -- interior 1948 (Box 4)
          - 314 -- Morrill's office supplies -- interior displays 1952, 4 negatives (Box 4)
          - 316 -- Wahr's Book Store -- display windows 1950, 3 negatives (Box 4)
          - 318-320 -- Quarry Drug
            - Exterior June 21, 1937 (Box 4)
            - Interior with people 1945 (Box 4)
            - Pharmacists at work 1948 (Box 4)
            - Display window June 26, 1952 (Box 4)
            - Interior with people 1952, 8 negatives (Box 4)
            - Display window April 27, 1953 (Box 4)
          - 322 -- M Hut restaurant circa 1930 (Box 4)
          - 324 -- Calkins-Fletcher Drug
            - circa 1928-1930 (Box 4)
            - circa 1930 (Box 4)
            - Interior February 23, 1938 (Box 4)
            - Interior October 30, 1939 (Box 4)
            - Window display July 21, 1940 (Box 4)
            - Window display September 1, 1940 (Box 4)
            - Window display October 12, 1940 (Box 4)
          - 326-330 -- Nickels Arcade
            - Arcade Knitting Shop September 5, 1941 (Box 4)
            - Bay's Jewelry -- interior circa October 1935 (Box 4)
            - Randall (Frederick S.) Travel Agency May 7, 1935 (Box 4)
            - Van Boven Shop
              - Interior circa 1942, 2 negatives (Box 4)
              - Interior circa 1943 (Box 4)
              - Interior with salesmen and window display 1951, 2 negatives (Box 4)
          - 714 -- apartment interior? May 18, 1940 (Box 4)
          - 808 -- Bermuda Restaurant -- exterior and interior January 3, 1955, 3 negatives (Box 4)
          - 818 -- Calkins-Fletcher Drug
            - circa 1930 (Box 4)
            - 1949 (Box 4)
          - 900 -- State Drug
            - 1951, 2 negatives (Box 4)
            - Window display 1953 (Box 4)
          - 1643 -- A.H. Payeur and Son Foundation Company 1953, 2 negatives (Box 4)
          - 1649 -- Gulf Refining Company September 9, 1936 (Box 4)
          - 1791 -- Townsend and Bottum, Inc., General Contractors -- exterior and interior 1949, 2 negatives (Box 4)
          - 2205 -- house June 1, 1955, 3 negatives (Box 4)
          - 2500 (Box 4)
            (See: Ann Arbor Businesses -- Edwards Brothers)
          - 2800 -- Crobalt Company 1950, 2 negatives (Box 4)
          - Unidentified estate -- house and yard March 28, 1955, 6 negatives (Box 4)
        - Sunset
          - 915 -- Pentuck house November 26, 1955 (Box 4)
        - Tappan
          - 718 -- Delta Delta Delta house October 1, 1939
            (See also: University of Michigan -- Student Life -- Fraternities and Sororities)
          - 836 (Box 4)
            (See: University of Michigan -- Student Life -- Fraternities and Sororities -- Pi Beta Phi)
        - Thayer-300
          - Music Center
            - 1949 (Box 4)
            - September 1953 (Box 4)
          - Vogue Beauty Salon 1953 (Box 4)
        - University, East
          - 547-549 -- Ulrich's Books
            - 1949 (and Wikel Drug) (Box 4)
            - 1950 (and Wikel Drug) (Box 4)
            - December 29, 1959 (Box 4)
          - 1001 -- Tappan Park East -- apartments
            - circa 1965, 4 negatives (Box 4)
            - circa 1966 (Box 4)
        - University, North
          - 711-717 -- storefronts (George J. Moe, Alexander, Inc, Hat Box, Goodyear's College Shop) circa 1936 (Box 4)
          - 715 -- Doe's Barbers 1951, 2 negatives (Box 4)
          - 715-727 -- storefronts (Goodyear's, Trojan Laundry, Miller Drug) circa 1936 (Box 4)
          - 727 -- Alexander Drug 1951 (Box 4)
          - 1005 -- Prettyman house (being wrecked) November 1, 1938, 2 negatives (Box 4)
          - 1319 -- George Woodard house and shop February 16, 1937 (Box 4)
        - University, South
          - 1100 -- Ann Arbor Bank (from Engineering Arch) circa 1965 (Box 4)
          - 1101 -- Calkins-Fletcher Drug circa 1930 (Box 4)
          - 1106 -- Hillbilly Hamburgers -- interior August 28, 1939, 3 negatives (Box 4)
          - 1107 -- Tice and Wren Store for Men 1952 (Box 4)
          - 1108 -- Laura Belle Shop December 10, 1937 (Box 4)
          - 1112 -- Carlson Drug -- exterior and interior 1952, 2 negatives (Box 4)
          - 1126 -- Manausa Motors -- exterior, staff and trucks 1948, 2 negatives (Box 4)
          - 1202 (Box 4)
          - 1225 -- University Drug, Miller Drug, and other storefronts August 3, 1954, 4 negatives (Box 4)
          - 1225-1233 -- University Towers April 13, 1966, 2 negatives (Box 4)
          - 1319 -- Student Bike Shop May 8, 1959, 2 negatives (Box 4)
        - Valley Drive -- 3011 -- house 1952, 5 negatives (Box 4)
        - Vesper -- 912 -- house, 1953, 3 negatives (in 2 envelope) (Box 4)
        - Vinewood -- 1827 -- house 1952 (Box 4)
        - Washington, East
          - 108 -- Brookins Smart Shoes -- interior September 7, 1940 (Box 4)
          - 114 -- Bimbo's Pizza -- exterior and interior with band and patrons circa 1965, 11 negatives (in 9 envelope) (Box 4)
          - 121-123 -- Capitol Market 1948 (Box 4)
          - 201 -- Washington Market 1932 (Box 4)
            [see also 8"x10" negative and print]
          - 219-223 -- Fischer's Hardware 1952 (Box 4)
          - 319 -- Michigan Bell 1948, 3 negatives (Box 4)
          - 400 (Box 4)
          - 401 -- Finance Center circa 1956 (Box 4)
          - 502-504 -- Ann Arbor Motor Sales and Service -- exterior and interior with workers 1952, 11 negatives (Box 4)
          - 502 -- Coffey Cadillac -- exterior and interior circa 1963, 4 negatives (Box 4)
          - 514 -- Herb Estes Ford 1950s (Box 4)
        - Washington, West
          - 123 -- Griswold Hotel (later the Earl Hotel) -- exterior and bedroom 1949, 3 negatives (Box 5)
          - 210 -- Town Club -- interior with patrons, waitresses, cooks circa 1956, 7 negatives (Box 5)
          - 215 -- Municipal Parking Structure 1953, 2 negatives (Box 5)
        - Washtenaw
          - 1437 (Box 5)
            (See: University of Michigan -- Student Life -- Fraternities and Sororities -- Phi Delta Theta)
          - 1705 -- house
            - May 4, 1938 (Box 5)
            - Chi Psi January 15, 1940, 2 negatives (Box 5)
            - Chi Psi, October 22 1940 (Box 5)
            - Chi Psi circa 1948 (Box 5)
            - Chi Psi 1952 (Box 5)
          - 1746(?) -- house May 4, 1938 (Box 5)
          - 1830
            - House March 14, 1937 (Box 5)
            - Women's City Club -- exterior and interior circa 1960s, 4 negatives (Box 5)
          - 2006 -- Zeta Beta Tau house March 17, 1956, 2 negatives (Box 5)
          - 2011 -- house 1949, 2 negatives (Box 5)
          - 3038 (Box 5)
            (See: Ann Arbor -- Businesses -- Winter Seal Company)
          - 3045 -- Herb Estes Ford May 8, 1959, 2 negatives (Box 5)
          - 3120 -- Warner Dairy circa 1951 (Box 5)
          - 3250 -- drawing of Inn America March 9, 1962 (Box 5)
          - 3345 -- house August 17, 1955 (Box 5)
          - 3451 -- Goodyear Auto Service Center August 16, 1967, 5 negatives (Box 5)
          - 4705 -- Royall, Inc. September 14, 1954, 2 negatives (Box 5)
        - Wesley -- 304 -- Blaess house February 20, 1942 (Box 5)
        - Westfield --1505 -- Chet Nowland house 1954, 2 negatives (Box 5)
        - Wildwood -- 231 -- Russell Hart house 1953 (Box 5)
        - William, East
          - 508 -- Lyon and Healy Music -- display window and interior 1948, 3 negatives (Box 5)
          - 517 -- popcorn stand with clerk and patron October 10, 1937, 2 negatives (Box 5)
          - 520-522 -- Maynard House 1964 (Box 5)
          - 611 -- College Shoe Repair -- interior 1948, 2 negatives (Box 5)
        - William, West
          - 216 -- Feiner Paint Store -- exterior and interior 1949-1950, 2 negatives (Box 5)
          - 221 (Box 5)
            (See: Ann Arbor -- Buildings and Views -- Railroad Stations and Trains -- Ann Arbor Railroad Freight House)
          - Unidentified house April 1966, 6 negatives (Box 5)
        - Wilton
          - 207 -- house April 26, 1957, 2 negatives (Box 5)
          - 303 -- Henry Grieser and house circa 1953, 2 negatives (Box 5)
        - Woodside Road -- house August 20, 1941 (Box 5)
        - Wright -- 1125 -- Feldkamp house December 15, 1969 (Box 5)
        - Miscellaneous (mostly unidentified)
          - Apartment Buildings
            - Interior 1953, 4 negatives (Box 5)
            - Two buildings 1962, 2 negatives (Box 5)
            - 1963 (Box 5)
            - April 16, 1964, 2 negatives (Box 5)
            - circa 1964, 4 negatives (Box 5)
            - circa 1966 (Box 5)
            - circa 1970 (Box 5)
          - Houses
            - circa 1935 (Box 5)
            - Tudor House circa 1935-1940 (Box 5)
            - Exteriors and interior circa 1940, 5 negatives (Box 5)
            - Berg house November 1946, 2 negatives (Box 5)
            - Brown's house December 1946 (Box 5)
            - Les Miller house 1949 (Box 5)
            - Exterior and interior circa 1949, 3 negatives (Box 5)
            - circa 1950
              - Bill Davis house (1218 Birk or 408 S. Seventh (Box 5)
              - 2824?) (Box 5)
            - circa 1951-1952, 5 negatives (Box 5)
            - circa 1952, 3 negatives (Box 5)
            - Mrs. James' house June 28, 1954 (Box 5)
            - Kitchen interior circa June 1955 (Box 5)
            - Exterior and interior circa 1956, 2 negatives (Box 5)
            - circa 1957 (Box 5)
            - circa 1959 (Box 5)
            - 1963, 2 negatives (Box 5)
            - February 2, 1966 (Box 5)
            - circa 1970 (Box 5)
          - Realtors' photographs of houses
            - Brooks-Newton Realty April 13, 1940, 3 negatives (Box 5)
              (different houses)
            - French, Ruth
              - May 29, 1942, 2 negatives (Box 5)
              - 1952, 5 negatives, different houses (Box 5)
              - circa 1953, 6 negatives, different houses (Box 5)
            - Randolph Realty 1952 exterior and interior, 4 negatives (Box 5)
          - Subdivisions
            - Ann Arbor Woods July 12, 1957, 3 negatives (Box 5)
            - Huron River Valley Estates-site August 11, 1969, 3 negatives (in 2 envelope) (Box 5)
            - Unidentified, May 31 1950s, 8 negatives (Box 5)
      - Parks
        - Burns Park
          - athletic team 1930s (Box 5)
          - Burns Park Log Cabin, undated (Box 5)
        - Island Park
          - 1945 (Box 5)
          - 1946, 2 negatives (Box 5)
      - Public Buildings
        - City Dump
          - 1952, 12 negatives (Box 5)
          - Mulreed Dump March 31, 1955, 5 negatives (Box 5)
          - With trucks March 17, 1960, 4 negatives (Box 5)
          - March 24, 1960, 3 negatives (Box 5)
        - Court House (County) -- being wrecked May 29, 1956, 4 negatives (Box 5)
        - Public Library -- William and Fifth September 23, 1957 (Box 5)
        - Sewage Disposal Plant
          - 1949 construction, 33 negatives (Box 5)
          - 1951 interior, 2 negatives (Box 5)
        - Water Softening Plant circa 1938 (Box 5)
      - Railroad Stations and Trains
        - Ann Arbor Railroad Freight House, 221 W. William circa 1950 (Box 5)
        - Railroad Station -- Carey Street
          (See also: Ann Arbor -- World War II; University of Michigan -- Athletics -- Football; University of Michigan -- Colleges, Schools, and other Divisions -- Broadcasting Service)
          - December 3, 1937 (Box 5)
          - circa 1940 (Box 5)
          - 1940s, 2 negatives (Box 5)
          - Train arrival December 1946, 3 negatives (Box 5)
          - Train arrival circa 1950 (Box 5)
          - Magazine rack October 30, 1957 (Box 5)
        - Trains and Wrecks (Not necessarily in Ann Arbor)
          - Union Pacific car circa 1935 (Box 5)
          - Wreck -- Ann Arbor Railroad Station, early 1940s, 2 negatives (Box 5)
          - Train March 20, 1942 (Box 5)
          - July 23, 1969, 6 negatives (in 3 envelope) (Box 5)
      - Schools
        - Angell
          - Exterior 1936, 2 negatives (Box 5)
          - July 10, 1937 (Box 5)
          - First grade class June 16, 1954 (Box 5)
        - Ann Arbor High School
          - Exterior 1930s (Box 5)
          - Exterior July 10, 1937 (Box 5)
          - Bicycles behind building October 26, 1937 (Box 5)
          - Auditorium and gymnasium January 14, 1938, 3 negatives (Box 5)
          - Exterior March 27, 1938, 2 negatives (Box 5)
          - Exterior October 25, 1938 (Box 5)
          - Addition at Thayer and Washington circa 1940 (Box 5)
          - Flag raising June 10, 1941, 2 negatives (Box 5)
          - Teachers? circa 1949 (Box 5)
          - Alumni dance at VFW hall December 26, 1953, 11 negatives (Box 5)
          - Plaque re. Argus Planetarium July 1956 (Box 5)
          - Class of 1942 June 15, 1957 (Box 5)
          - Class of 1928 reunion at Weber's June 5, 1963 (Box 5)
        - Ann Arbor Secretarial School
          - Classes September 15, 1942, 2 negatives (Box 5)
          - Graduation November 13, 1942 (Box 5)
        - Bach Elementary School
          - Exterior July 10, 1937 (Box 5)
          - Exterior November 1, 1937 (Box 5)
          - Children in classes; library; plays December 8, 1937, 30 negatives (Box 5)
          - Christmas play December 20, 1940 (Box 5)
          - Exterior 1952 (Box 5)
        - Carpenter -- exterior and teachers circa 1954 (Box 5)
        - Concordia Lutheran Junior College -- dormitory exterior and interior March 2, 1970, 9 negatives (Box 5)
        - Eberwhite Elementary School
          - Teacher and students circa 1952 (Box 5)
          - Exterior July 1953 (Box 5)
        - Fritz Elementary -- exterior circa 1956 (Box 5)
        - Jones School
          - Exterior July 10, 1937 (Box 5)
          - Mary Lee Hart's kindergarten class April 4, 1940 (Box 5)
          - Exterior 1952, 2 negatives (in 1 envelope) (Box 5)
        - Mack Elementary School
          - Exterior July 10, 1937, 2 negatives (Box 5)
          - Teachers 1950 (Box 5)
          - Christmas tree and children circa 1951 (Box 5)
          - Entry with children (exterior) circa 1952 (Box 5)
        - Northwest Elementary School -- under construction 1953-1954, 10 negatives (Box 5)
        - Pioneer High School -- auditorium, man and woman 1956, 3 negatives (Box 5)
        - St. Thomas
          - Basketball team March 11, 1940, 2 negatives (Box 6)
          - Football team circa 1940 (Box 6)
          - Yearbook pictures March 1955, 12 negatives (Box 6)
          - Dance and queen October 14, 1955, 4 negatives (Box 6)
          - Christmas pageant December 20, 1955, 9 negatives (Box 6)
          - Exterior and students boarding bus January 20, 1956, 5 negatives (Box 6)
          - Baseball team March 3, 1956 (Box 6)
          - Latin week April 15, 1956, 2 negatives (Box 6)
          - Athletic banquet May 16, 1956, 3 negatives (Box 6)
          - Students on bus October 8, 1956, 3 negatives (Box 6)
          - Football players, cheerleaders, wrestlers October 1956, 9 negatives (Box 6)
          - Homecoming couples and dance October 12, 1956, 9 negatives (Box 6)
          - 1956
            - Christmas play, 4 negatives (Box 6)
            - Library, 3 negatives (Box 6)
            - School scenes, 6 negatives (Box 6)
          - Speakers, classroom, students circa 1956, 9 negatives (Box 6)
          - Interior with students and teachers January 29, 1957, 5 negatives (Box 6)
          - Exteriors, students, and dance February 14, 1957, 6 negatives (Box 6)
          - Valentine dance February 18, 1957, 5 negatives (Box 6)
          - Athletic banquet May 28, 1957, 3 negatives (Box 6)
          - Graduation June 9, 1957 (Box 6)
          - Halloween dance October 31, 1957, 2 negatives (Box 6)
          - Homecoming football game cheerleaders and dance November 9, 1957, 13 negatives (Box 6)
          - Christmas pageant December 13, 1957, 8 negatives (Box 6)
          - circa 1957
            - Broadcasting -- WHRV (Box 6)
            - Golf class and girls' and boys' sports teams, 6 negatives (Box 6)
            - Pep Rally, 3 negatives (Box 6)
            - School scenes and group photos, 25 negatives (Box 6)
            - Students and bus (Box 6)
            - Students and priest (Box 6)
            - Students, classes, cheerleaders, 11 negatives (Box 6)
          - Yearbook photos March 19, 1958, 6 negatives (Box 6)
          - Bill Carey with children May 18, 1959, 3 negatives (Box 6)
        - Slauson Junior High
          - Auditorium circa 1938, 3 negatives (Box 6)
          - Exterior April 13, 1939 (Box 6)
          - Exterior 1952 (Box 6)
        - Tappan Junior High
          - Exterior, Summer 1937 (Box 6)
          - July 10, 1937 (Box 6)
          - Exterior November 1, 1937 (Box 6)
          - Exterior with Burns Park and tennis courts, late circa 1930s (Box 6)
          - School lunch program circa 1950 (Box 6)
          - Exterior and interiors (gymnasium, classroom, home economics room) 1952, 4 negatives (Box 6)
        - University Elementary School. (Box 6)
          (See: University of Michigan -- Colleges, Schools, and Other Divisions -- Education School)
        - University High School. (Box 6)
        - Wines Elementary -- assembly circa 1957 (Box 6)
        - Miscellaneous
          - Girls with slide rule and Weston Volt-meter circa 1940, 2 negatives (Box 6)
          - Ann Arbor School Board 1951, 2 negatives (Box 6)
          - Mrs. Collins' class circa November 1954 (Box 6)
          - Teacher placement banquet December 2, 1954 (Box 6)
          - Safety campaign -- Ann Arbor Public Schools and Automobile Club of Michigan August 20, 1969, 2 negatives (in 1 envelope) (Box 6)
        - Unidentified schools -- 1937 circa 1940s, 1952, 5 negatives of 3 schools (Box 6)
      - Streets
        - Baldwin Place 1949, 2 negatives (Box 6)
        - Bird Road circa 1951 (Box 6)
        - Broadway Bridge circa 1956, 2 negatives (Box 6)
        - Brooklyn at Ferdon April 26, 1957 (Box 6)
        - Country Club Road (Barton Hills entry) October 17, 1956, 2 negatives (Box 6)
        - Crest at Washington 1951 (Box 6)
        - Division, South
          - 300 block August 16, 1965 (Box 6)
          - 400 block April 28, 1964 (Box 6)
        - Duncan Street (Box 6)
        - Edgewood Avenue April 26, 1954, 4 negatives (Box 6)
        - Felch at Miner 1957, 3 negatives (Box 6)
        - Ferdon at Brooklyn April 26, 1957 (Box 6)
        - Fifth Avenue, South, at Liberty 1963, 2 negatives (Box 6)
        - First at William circa 1950 (Box 6)
        - Forest Avenue at South University 1964, 2 negatives (Box 6)
        - Fuller Road near Wall Street 1946, 2 negatives (Box 6)
        - Geddes
          - at Awixa November 29, 1941 (Box 6)
          - at Linden 1963, 2 negatives (Box 6)
        - Hogback Road circa 1963, 2 negatives (Box 6)
        - Huron River Drive, ca. 1931, 5 negatives (Box 6)
        - Huron Street, East
          - at Fifth October 22, 1940 (Box 6)
          - at Fifth November 1940 (Box 6)